module.exports = {
  gameType: 'text',
  questions: [
    {
      question: 'what game do frank and charlie play in their apartment?', 
      a: 'tummy sticks', 
      b: 'night crawlers',
      c: 'tickle monster',
      d: 'pickle toss',
      answer: 'b'
    },
    {
      question: 'who does charlie have a crush on?', 
      a: 'the waitress', 
      b: 'dee',
      c: 'artemis',
      d: 'margaret mcpoyle',
      answer: 'a'
    },
    {
      question: 'mac refers to his rapid weight gain as', 
      a: 'paying the swoll toll', 
      b: 'cultivating mass',
      c: 'baking the beef cake',
      d: 'compound muscle interest',
      answer: 'b'
    },
    {
      question: 'the gang tries to break whose record by drinking 70 beers on a cross-country flight?', 
      a: 'rob dibble', 
      b: 'brett favre',
      c: 'john daly',
      d: 'wade boggs',
      answer: 'd'
    },
    {
      question: 'where does the gang hide their booze to publicly drink at the jersey shore?', 
      a: 'in sunscreen bottles', 
      b: 'in diet coke cans',
      c: 'in fake colostomy bags',
      d: 'in a water melon',
      answer: 'a'
    },
    {
      question: 'which member of the gang is not in season one?', 
      a: 'mac', 
      b: 'dennis',
      c: 'charlie',
      d: 'frank',
      answer: 'd'
    },
    {
      question: 'who do mac and charlie decide should play the lead in the movie they write?', 
      a: 'dolf lundgren', 
      b: 'mel gibson',
      c: 'frank stallone',
      d: 'steven segal',
      answer: 'a'
    },
    {
      question: 'charlie is a survivor of what:', 
      a: 'a plane crash', 
      b: 'cancer',
      c: 'abortion',
      d: 'paint huffing overdose',
      answer: 'c'
    },
    {
      question: 'what is the name of the gang\'s bar?', 
      a: 'paddy\'s pub', 
      b: 'cheers',
      c: 'the bearded clam',
      d: 'moe\'s',
      answer: 'a'
    },
    {
      question: 'the cincy office moves to the official ACN location in the beginning of', 
      a: 'february', 
      b: 'march',
      c: 'april',
      d: 'may',
      answer: 'd'
    }
  ]
};